<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog Archive on Eboxi notes and experiments</title><link>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/</link><description>Recent content in Blog Archive on Eboxi notes and experiments</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:30:17 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beomaster 4000 Lamp Replacement</title><link>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beomaster4000lamps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:30:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beomaster4000lamps/</guid><description>A simple way to replace the B&amp;amp;O filament lamps with LED's
Background (Note this was first published on beoworld.org in 2021 but they removed the old posts) Like a lot older B&amp;amp;O systems, the Beomaster 4000 uses filament lamps. In most of the vintage B&amp;amp;O's these lamps are soldered but the lamps in the Beomaster 4000 fits into a holder. An ideal replacement would be LED's that directly fit into these holders.</description></item><item><title>Beomaster 4000 Power Switch Repair</title><link>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beo4swfix/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 14:30:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beo4swfix/</guid><description>Fixing the power switch
(This is just a copy of the text original published on the Beoworld that was unfortunately removed)
A broken switch often starts off with some intermittent on/off switching. Normally the resistance across the switch contacts is higher than expected (less than about 2-3 ohm I would guess is normal) or vary a lot (5-25 ohm in my case).
Unfortunately replacements are not available, unless you can find a second hand one.</description></item><item><title>Beomaster 4000 Power Switch Removal</title><link>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beo4swremove/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 14:30:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://otto-eboxi.github.io/blogarc/beo4swremove/</guid><description>Removing the power switch
(This is just a copy of the text original published on the Beoworld that was unfortunately removed)
The power switch on some of the Beomaster's tend to fail. I could not find instructions how to remove it anywhere, so in case it will help anyone this is how I removed mine.
Step 1:Open the unit, remove and disassemble the front panel
The front panel is tricky because its got lots of screws and some are hidden and in difficult positions (maybe I will do a post about it later)</description></item></channel></rss>